he's a he's aligning relationships on
surface things
versus grounding them
in the depths of our spirit that made me
think about um kevin samuels why why do
you think about kevin samuels
in terms of in terms of what i think he
i wasn't subscribed so for the record i
wasn't wondering i was gonna say he
better put a disclaimer quick i'm not
one of his followers um but when i do
talk to people that have been in tune
with his messaging
it does seem from the outside he was
trying to
i guess uh
what's the word balance out the the
criticism kind of even the playing field
is that what he was trying to do
in in hindsight of
men
who
let me put this in let me put this right
black men we are raised in a matriarch
society you're not raised in a
matriarchal society though that's false
i mean just because you're raised by a
woman doesn't mean you're raised in a
matriarchal society in our in our
community i was raised by a single
mother in a patriarchal society
okay
but in my experience this is my
experience no but i'm telling you like
your experience doesn't change the
society that we're in okay even though
you were raised by a woman she's raising
you within a patriarchal framework there
what i let me try to express women
aren't like she wasn't raising you
within a space where women are leaders
that are revered
and
like that you should aspire like that's
not what we're in i'm just laying up
what i think these brothers are coming
from ah fair okay
okay
i'm not okay
and i think that i despise them
i think that those
brothers who
don't maybe have the strongest
self-esteem or the
strongest awareness of how to lead
a woman in a healthy way
um at times maybe felt pushed to the
side
felt discredited because they didn't
have a certain status and i think with a
guy like kevin samuels
they gravitated towards him because he
was now holding women accountable
more than we've ever really seen it
it wasn't delivered the best
but i can live from the outside
that is
i'm gonna have to go completely against
that okay uh so why do you think people
were i think this like people were
listening to him because we're in a
[ __ ] up society
and he was confirmation bias for their
support that's why
the same reason that people are mad at
me because i'm affirming a truth that's
inconvenient to their
right so they're like that [ __ ]
she's making me feel some type of way
i don't want to feel some type of way
and who is she to make me feel some type
of way but the way you feel that i'm
making you feel
is because it's a truth that you know
but you have to deal with it and you're
not ready to deal with it because if you
deal with it it's going to bring up a
whole bunch of other [ __ ] properly that
you have to deal with and you don't
necessarily have the support system
around you
or the tools to be able to do so
and that is the fault of
our whole social network right but
this idea of holding women accountable
mm-hmm
it's a to me it's a false equivalency
because it sound the reason why he came
up is because you said that
and this is only me seeing clips like
highlights of his work oh i've seen
a lot okay
so you you're probably more of an expert
in this space than me
but it did seem like you were saying the
thing of like women having these like
crazy expectations that they don't
necessarily apply to themself and it
felt like he was trying to do the same
thing from the clips i saw but the thing
is is that i'm i'm basing that
on
value systems
integrity
right your ethics he's basing that on
materialism
on
your outward appearance
and on status
so
he's trying to he was
doing what i think is a very big
disservice to folks because
he's
he's a he's aligning relationships on
surface things
versus grounding them
in the depths of our spirit
and those surface things that he's
that he was you know basing things on
ultimately end up
being about greed
and being about
just
things that don't carry you through when
you really are dealing with life
your looks
your money
your status
when your mom dies
what's that gonna like it may mean that
you can bury her in the coffin if you
want
if your child is born with a disability
it may mean that you can get them the
care that you want because you have some
money but
so talk to the lower frequency
the high vibration is
you i mean i'm emotional right now the
high vibration
is you consistently challenging yourself
to live in light
and all those things that he was talking
about are not about that
it's not about that because
you want to be with somebody that loves
what's inside of you this is a show
like you want to you want to be and you
want to be with friends like that's
really what it is but we are in a
society that is so focused on this
outward appearance image appearance et
cetera et cetera
and i'm in a business that that's based
on right like in show biz in hollywood
like it's so much about like how you
look i remember keen ivory wayans like
on last comic standing like telling aida
rodriguez that her yellow dress was
distracting from her telling jokes
like
that's a you problem bruh like
that's a you problem
she's being funny and you talking about
a yellow dress because you're attracted
to her and you can't
hear her funniness over your dick